const questions = [
    {
        'question': 'String values must be enclosed within ______ when being assigned to variables.',
        'answers': ['commas','curly brackets','quotes','parentheses'],
        'correct_index': 2
    }, {
        'question': 'A very useful tool used during development and debugging for printing content to the debugger is:',
        'answers': ['for loops','console.log','terminal / bash','JavaScript'],
        'correct_index': 1
    }, {
        'question': 'Commonly used data types DO NOT include:',
        'answers': ['alerts','numbers','strings','booleans'],
        'correct_index': 0
    }, {
        'question': 'The condition in an if/else statement is enclosed within ______.',
        'answers': ['quotes','curly brackets','square brackets','parentheses'],
        'correct_index': 3
    }, {
        'question': 'Which program is used by web clients to view the web pages?',
        'answers': ['Web browser','Protocol','Web server','Search Engine'],
        'correct_index': 0
    }, {
        'question': 'The ______ attribute is used to identify the values of variables.',
        'answers': ['text','http-equiv','content','name'],
        'correct_index': 2
    }, {
        'question': 'Which tag is used to identify the keywords describing the site?',
        'answers': ['Comment tag','Title tag','Meta tag','Anchor tag'],
        'correct_index': 2
    }, {
        'question': 'Which are used with a tag to modify its function?',
        'answers': ['Files','Functions','Attributes','Documents'],
        'correct_index': 2
    }, {
        'question': 'This is a declaration that IS NOT an html tag.  it is an instruction to the web browser about what version of HTML a web page is written in.',
        'answers': ['html','doctype','head','body'],
        'correct_index': 1
    }, {
        'question': 'Content information that appears between the oppening and closing ______ tags will show up in a browser view.',
        'answers': ['body','html','head','table'],
        'correct_index': 0
    }, 
]
